brainhunter.com 2010-12-24

# Brainhunter :: Privacy

**ZYLOG SYSTEMS LIMITED (ZYLOG) PRIVACY POLICY**

Privacy of our user's information is of utmost importance at Zylog. First and foremost, Zylog is fully compliant with the Canadian Privacy Legislation. Moreover, we strive to provide a safe, confidential and secure system so that you feel comfortable storing your information with us. We understand the highly confidential nature of the employment search process, and our policies are designed to give you the control you need to ensure complete confidentiality.   

**INFORMATION GATHERED**   

**_ANONYMOUS BROWSING_**   
Zylog uses your IP address to help track where you came from, what services you are using, to help us administer our web site, and to improve our services.   

**USE OF COOKIES**   

We also use "cookies" to track your use of the site, and to ensure that you are a valid, registered user throughout your "session".   

**PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTION, USE AND DISTRIBUTION TO THIRD PARTIES**   

**GENERALLY**   

Zylog gathers the personal information required to be of service and to complete the transactions contemplated in the use of our service. Generally, the information gathered from you is used to assist you in your career search or search for employment. As such, it may require us to release your personal information with your consent to third parties. These third parties may be in Canada or in other parts of the world. By registering with Zylog, you agree that your information may be shared with third parties for the purpose of satisfying your requests and transactions related to it.   

We generally collect information contained in your resume such as name, address, home phone number, work phone number, cellular telephone number(s), facsimile numbers, email addresses and general contact information to facilitate employers, recruiters and Zylog to be able to readily communicate with you. We also collect additional personal information such as career objectives and restrictions, as well as your resume and skills (your "information").   

We collect and may disclose statistical information gathered as a whole (e.g. Total number of job-seekers, total number of IT job seekers) for marketing purposes and to improve the services to our clients. However, we never disclosure information on an individual basis for such purposes. We may also use, disclose and communicate your personal information if required to do so by law including by an order of any court.   

Zylog uses all reasonable means to ensure that third party sources uses your personal information only for the purposes for which it was provided and in adherence to the Zylog’s Privacy Policy. However, Zylog is not responsible for any improper use of your personal information that is beyond our reasonable control.   

We do not knowingly solicit information from children and we do not knowingly market our services to children.   

**THIRD PARTY LINKS**   

Zylog Ltd. contains links to other sites. Although we strive to provide links to sites that have similar privacy policies and practices that respect user privacy, we are not responsible for the practices or the content of these sites.   

**YOUR RESUME INFORMATION**   

Your contact information (name, address, phone number, etc) is kept confidential by default, until you "ok" its release to an employer by allowing yourself to be submitted to a job (a process you control fully) or by applying directly to a job. By default, your resume is ‘viewable’ by recruiters if they do a manual search of our database. This ‘viewable’ resume does not contain any contact information such as your name, address, phone number or email addresses.   

You can BLOCK companies from being able to see ANY information including your resume in a manual search. If you select this option, employers will only see your name and resume once you agree to be submitted to a job, or apply directly. More information on this feature is available in our HELP screens.   

We do not disclose your information to anyone except as described above, including personal information, resume information, email addresses, information about your visits to the site, etc.   

**DISCLOSURE OF EMPLOYER INFORMATION**   

Zylog does disclose portions of the company information gathered during the employer sign-up including Company Name, Location of Job, Headquarters, Annual Revenue, Web Site Address, Company Address, Stock Information without consent. This information where provided, is made available to job seekers to increase their knowledge of your firm. We do NOT disclose any contact information, or individual user information.   

You have the option of posting "Confidential" jobs, where no company information will be shown on the site, and will only be disclosed on a personal basis to each pre-screened, interested candidate. More information on these features is available in our HELP screens.   

**ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**   

Your personal information is stored on a secure server hosted by Zylog. The server resides in Zylog’s data center that resides in the province of Ontario, Canada.   

You may access your personal information anytime by visiting Zylog’s website at www.brainhunter.com and logging into Zylog’s system using you user id and password. You may add, change or delete any personal information at any time, on your own. If you have any questions at any time regarding the update or deletion of your personal information, you may obtain help by calling our support hotline at 1-877-4-EBRAIN or by sending us an e-mail with your request at support@brainhunter.com.   

**HOW IS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURED AND PROTECTED?**   

Zylog’s data resides in servers in our data center in Canada. We use commercially reasonable measures to physically protect access to our equipment. Additionally, our servers reside behind firewalls to protect against intrusion and hacking.   

Sensitive information such as credit card number input by you and transmitted by us is encrypted using Secured Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. We do not store you credit card information on our servers.   

Information transmitted by you to us is usually done in clear text (not encrypted). We would therefore caution you not to send highly sensitive information through e-mail. However, transactions done on our website are done using SSL and are encrypted and secure.   

Zylog’s new system, expected to roll out in the first quarter of 2005. This system has an even higher security standard using HTTPS and SSL for the collection and transmission of all information (not just sensitive or critical information).   

Zylog instructs all of our employees that information collected on our site must be used with the strictest adherence to our Privacy Policy and applicable Federal and Provincial laws.   

**FEEDBACK AND SUGGESTIONS**   

Zylog encourages feedback and suggestions for improvement. Any feedback or suggestions submitted become the property of Zylog. Feedback and comments may be submitted to: **[support@brainhunter.com. ](mailto:support@brainhunter.com)**
